Gregoire MALZAC 166 Haverstock Hill, NW3 2AT London +33 6 63 95 70 32 gregoire.malzac@gmail.com

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/gregoire-malzac/?locale=en_US

https://github.com/GMalzac

After **7+ years of management consulting** in financial services developping *soft* skills and my knowlege of the banking sector, I have completed a coding bootcamp (Le Wagon) in London.

I now aim at using my newly acquired skills - combined with the set of skills I learned as a consultant – as a full-stack developper. Looking for dynamism and ambitious challenges, I am available starting mid-may.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

From March 2018 Freelance full-stack developper, London

1 month 1/2 UX improvement, website performance optimization and hosting problems trouble shooting for

www.guepesetpapillons.fr

Design, sketching and development of an MVP to help travellers store their travel information in one place

to retrieve them easily during their trip: www.journease.online

From 2014 to December 2017

8 months

Financial Services Consulting, Manager

Pecember 2017 WEAVE, Paris

Examples of missions:

Strategic and Operationnal Program Management for the construction of a mutualized payment platform for

two major French banking actors (Societe Generale and La Banque Postale)

⇒ Succeded in gettingh

4 months Strategic Study for the implementation of the Instant Credit Transfer (Instant Payment) for a major French

banking actor (Credit Agricole)

9 months PMO for the technical stream of a digital transformation program for one of the top-5 French banks (Société

Générale) consisting in deploying 75,000 tablets to employees worldwide

From 2010 to 2014 Financial Services Consulting, Consultant

HEADLINK-PARTNERS, Paris

Examples of missions:

4 months Construction and animation of a Global PMO cell to coordinate the steering of a portfolio of projects for a

major French banking actor (Natixis Asset Management)

7 months Definition and implementation of the Strategic Plan for a major Tunisian banking actor (Banque Tuniso-

Koweitienne, BPCE Group)

3 months Framing of the Change Management stream of a major transformation program for one of the top-5 French

banks (Société Générale)

June 2009 - Sales for a family wine company

June 2010 DOMAINE DE LA GENENTIERE, Paris

August 2008 - Sales assistant for the Private Banking team on derivative products, Front office COMMERZBANK, London

EDUCATIONAL QUALIFICATIONS

January 2018 - Coding bootcamp learning HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript ES2015, SQL, git, GitHub,

March 2018 Heroku and Ruby on Rails **Le Wagon, London,**

2004 – 2008 Master in Management, International Markets Finance

EDHEC Business School Lille-Nice, ranked #1 Master in Finance worldide by the

Financial Times rankings

SKILLS

Technical Ruby on Rails, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Javascript ES2015, SQL, git, Github and Heroku

Tools Office Suite (Powerpoint, Excel, Word), Bloomberg, Reuters, Telekurs

English Fluent (TOEIC: 975)
Spanish Working knowledge

INTERESTS

Leisures Cooking and Reading

Sports Running (1h37 for Paris 20km race in 2017) and Hiking